http://www.jaguar.org.au/about-us/privacy.html

Jaguar Drivers Club of Australia
HomeJoinLinksConditional Historic RegistrationNational RallyAbout UsWelcomeHistoryFAQsJoinPrivacy PolicyCalendarRegistersHeritage RegisterClassic XKE TypeCompact SaloonsXJ SaloonsXJ CoupeGrand TourersModern SaloonsSportingIllawarra DistrictWestern DistrictPhotosClassifiedsCarsPartsWantedPlatesBooksHow to AdvertiseTerms of using this siteSuppliersLinksBecome a SupplierRegaliaContact UsCommittee MembersJoinPrivacy PolicyMembersUpdate DetailsUpdate PasswordCarsMembership RenewalJDCA Club MagazineConditional Historic RegistrationClub ContactsPresidents Honour RollConcours Honour RollTrophy Winner Honour RollSporting Trophy Honour RollCommittee Login
Welcome ,
You are here: About Us : Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
At The Jaguar Drivers Club of Australia (JDCA) we respect the privacy of every member of the JDCA and any individual who visits our website. JDCA is bound by the Privacy Act 1988) (Cth) (Privacy Act) including the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs), and applicable privacy regulations and is committed to protecting your privacy when managing your personal information and has policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is handled in accordance with the Privacy Act and the APPs.
This privacy statement provides notice of the standards and terms under which we protect the privacy of information supplied by members and visitors to our website.
This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this information.
The JDCA receives data about its members and website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when a member or visitor requests information or a quote, makes a purchase or sends us an e-mail.
When you provide personally identifiable information to us through our website, it will be used only to fulfil your specific request. We do reserve the right, at our discretion, to send you information about specials or services. We will not, however, sell or trade your personally identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so.
The JDCA takes all reasonable steps to ensure your information remains secure, and to prevent unauthorised access to your information. We use our best efforts to ensure that information received whether via this website or elsewhere remains secure within our systems, however users should be aware that there are inherent risks in transmitting information across the Internet. We are not responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.
JDCA treats complaints relating to privacy extremely seriously. If you submit a concern or complaint, we will endeavour to deal with it comprehensively and reach an outcome with which all parties are satisfied. If you are not satisfied with our response to your complaint (after providing us with a reasonable time to respond) or would like further information about privacy in Australia, then we suggest you contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner’s website.
The JDCA website does not use cookies to automatically gather information about you as a member or when you visit our website.
Due care and diligence is used in the preparation of the Australian Jaguar Driver magazine and this website, but no responsibility or liability is accepted for any mistake, misprint, omission or typographical error. No warranty or representation as to the truth, accuracy or sufficiency of photographs or statements in advertisements is given.
Opinions expressed in the Australian Jaguar Driver magazine are not necessarily those of the Club, its committees, members or of the Editor. For the detailed privacy policy of the JDCA, please click on the following link:
Privacy Policy (117 KB)
© 2019 Jaguar Drivers Club of Australia PO Box 1485. Macquarie Park NSW 2113.
